<Root Type="CustomLibrary">
  <Node Code="E/01">
    <Desc TranslateID="E/01_Desc">
      <ENU>Reinforcement cannot be designed. The position of reinforcement layers does not match the thickness of the member.</ENU>
    </Desc>
    <Sol TranslateID="E/01_Sol">
      <ENU>Decrease the concrete cover or increase the thickness of the 2D member.</ENU>
    </Sol>
  </Node>
  <Node Code="E/02">
    <Desc TranslateID="E/02_Desc">
      <ENU>Reinforcement cannot be designed. Internal forces are zero.</ENU>
    </Desc>
    <Sol TranslateID="E/02_Sol">
      <ENU>
      </ENU>
    </Sol>
  </Node>
  <Node Code="W/01">
    <Desc TranslateID="W/01_Desc">
      <ENU>The applied provided reinforcement is not sufficient for some of the layers (As,prov &lt; As,req).</ENU>
    </Desc>
    <Sol TranslateID="W/01_Sol">
      <ENU>Increase the amount of the basic or additional reinforcement.</ENU>
    </Sol>
  </Node>
  <Node Code="W/02">
    <Desc TranslateID="W/02_Desc">
      <ENU>The applied provided reinforcement exceeds the maximum limit (As,prov &gt; As,max).</ENU>
    </Desc>
    <Sol TranslateID="W/02_Sol">
      <ENU>Increase the thickness of the member or the quality of used materials.</ENU>
    </Sol>
  </Node>
  <Node Code="W/04">
    <Desc TranslateID="W/04_Desc">
      <ENU>The user-defined concrete cover is not sufficient for some of the surfaces (cuser &lt; cnom).</ENU>
    </Desc>
    <Sol TranslateID="W/04_Sol">
      <ENU>Increase the concrete cover or switch the method for the determination of the cover to 'Auto'.</ENU>
    </Sol>
  </Node>
  <Node Code="W/06">
    <Desc TranslateID="W/06_Desc">
      <ENU>The resistance of the virtual concrete strut is exhausted.</ENU>
    </Desc>
    <Sol TranslateID="W/06_Sol">
      <ENU>Change reinforcement geometry or increase the thickness of the member.</ENU>
    </Sol>
  </Node>
  <Node Code="W/03">
    <Desc TranslateID="W/03_Desc">
      <ENU>The designed required reinforcement exceeds the maximum limit (As,req &gt; As,max).</ENU>
    </Desc>
    <Sol TranslateID="W/03_Sol">
      <ENU>Increase the thickness of the member or the quality of used materials.</ENU>
    </Sol>
  </Node>
  <Node Code="W/07">
    <Desc TranslateID="W/07_Desc">
      <ENU>Punching shear resistance at the column perimeter (vRd,max) is not sufficient acc. to ยง6.4.3(2).</ENU>
    </Desc>
    <Sol TranslateID="W/07_Sol">
      <ENU>Increase the column size or change plate properties (use higher grade of concrete material or increase the thickness).</ENU>
    </Sol>
  </Node>
</Root>